# **Nicole How**

## **UI/UX Product Designer**

I'm a fourth-year design student enrolled in York University's honours bachelor of design program (BDes). My expertise is in UI/UX, but I also cover both digital and print-based media like packaging, and visual design. I value unique perspectives, ambitious goals, and a collaborative approach that promote continual learning. My focus is on designing human-centric and interactive creative solutions one pixel at a time!

## $\square$

how.nicole@hotmail.com



nicole-how.github.io/



behance.net/nicolehow



linkedin.com/in/nicole-how

### **EXPERIENCE**

## Office of Vice-President Research & Innovation

Graphic Design & Multimedia Assistant | 09/2023—(Current)

Designed brand-consistent print and digital materials for advertising campaigns, including banners, brochures, and engaging social media posts. Collaborated with manager to develop concepts that complied with creative briefs and brand guidelines. Enhanced service promotion efforts through visually engaging multimedia materials.

REFERENCE // Corey Allen | (upon request)

## **Open Farm Pet**

Graphic Design Internship | 05/2023 - 08/2023

Incorporated company's brand identity into a range of design formats, such as pitch sheets, email correspondence, and printed materials like product packaging. Collaborated with Senior Art Director and Graphic Designers to develop concepts, incorporating feedback to meet creative briefs and brand standards. Compiled and prepared printed presentation materials, ensuring a cohesive representation of the company's visual identity.

REFERENCE // Adam Pittman | Adam@openfarmpet.com

## Vibecheck

Product Designer | 05/2023 - 08/2023

Worked as lead Product Designer at startup. Collaborating with software engineers and operations teams in scrum meetings to discuss research and design for our application. Together, we translated AI features and product requirements into human-centric user friendly UI components, ensuring alignment with development capabilities and product requirements with our service in mind.

### **EDUCATION**

## Honours Bachelor Of Design York University

09/2020 - 04/2024 Awarded Entrance Scholarship

#### SKILLS

Design Thinking, Wireframing, Prototyping, Interaction Design, User Research & Testing, Task Flows, UI & UX, Information Design, Visual Identity, Typography, Branding

#### TOOLS

Figma & Figjam, Miro Adobe Suite [XD, Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop, Acrobat], HTML, CSS, Javascript, Webflow, Powerpoint, Maya

